{
    "id": "e01c6ad5c2f74d18a204148c8484eac0",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My father ………………….. at a bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3128d1a4a104b8191a3d0466d49f4b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brothers …………………. incredibly well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sing",
                "sings",
                "are singing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7230c2fb163c4b10818a0ee20c17406e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I always ………………… a bath before I go to bed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "am taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2559e9a3d9e24ae9bae5e914d91dc35d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Supriya ………………… English well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "speaks",
                "is speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b839684833a4945ac5cfaa7cfec7ee4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fd146fd00eaf43c281ceac00e1d712e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What are you doing there?’ ‘I …………………. a letter.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "am writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2139556d58d4f018f3eac724aecfb3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children …………………. a song.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sing",
                "are singing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa83f7a522434991ac863525165e5bd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rohan ………………….. his car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repair",
                "repairs",
                "is repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "91a33e3285d84a32be44bae8e2525983"
        },
        {
            "question": "The postman ………………….. the letters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "brings"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "69de27cc32a747c097e5bc149a1e48a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "am knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "edbe6a46fab8422a97925dc3e8570a94"
        }
    ]
}